Privacy Policy
==============

Effective Date: 2023-10-18

KeeperKeeperChat

General
-------

Keeper Security, Inc. ("Keeper Security") is fanatical about protecting your privacy. Keeper Security has created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our commitment to protecting your privacy and to disclose our information and privacy practices for [https://keepersecurity.com](https://keepersecurity.com/) and its services. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

We reserve the right to change this Policy and will notify you of such changes via email or our website. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at [security@keepersecurity.com](mailto:security@keepersecurity.com).

As used in this Privacy Policy, “personal data” or "personal information" has the meaning provided in the EU General Data Protection Regulation of 2018 (the “GDPR”), and includes any information which, either alone or when combined with other information we hold, identifies an individual, such as name, mailing address, email address, IP address and telephone number. For legal residents of the State of California, who are covered by the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”), this definition includes any additional elements defined as such by the CCPA. In addition to meeting GDPR and CCPA compliance requirements, the terms of this privacy policy are applicable to all users regardless of location.

Data Privacy Framework
----------------------

Keeper Security complies with the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (“EU-U.S. DPF”), the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF and the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (“Swiss-U.S. DPF”) as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce.

Keeper Security has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (“EU-U.S. DPF Principles”) with regard to the processing of personal data received from the European Union in reliance on the EU-U.S. DPF and from the United Kingdom (and Gibraltar) in reliance on the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF.

Keeper Security has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (“Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles”) with regard to the processing of personal data received from Switzerland in reliance on the Swiss-U.S. DPF.

If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the EU-U.S. DPF Principles and/or the Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles, the EU-U.S. DPF Principles and/or the Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Data Privacy Framework (“DPF”) program, and to view our certification, please visit [https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/).

Keeper Security is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under the EU-U.S. DPF, the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF, and Swiss-U.S. DPF and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. Keeper Security complies with the EU-U.S. DPF Principles and the Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU, UK, and Switzerland, including the onward transfer liability provisions.

The Federal Trade Commission has jurisdiction over Keeper Security’s compliance with the EU-U.S. DPF, the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF and the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (“Swiss-U.S. DPF”). Keeper Security does not have access to or knowledge of any account holder’s master password, encryption keys or access to their Keeper vault. Accordingly, any account disclosure required by law, under a subpoena, would be limited to general account information such as the account holder’s name and account term.

In compliance with the EU-U.S. DPF, the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF and the Swiss-U.S. DPF, Keeper Security commits to refer unresolved complaints concerning our handling of personal data received in reliance on EU-U.S. DPF, the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF and the Swiss-U.S. DPF to TRUSTe, an alternative dispute resolution provider based in the United States. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your DPF Principles-related complaint from us, or if we have not addressed your DPF Principles-related complaint to your satisfaction, please visit [https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request) for more information or to file a complaint. The services of TRUSTe are provided at no cost to you.

Under certain conditions, more fully described on the DPF website [https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/s/article/ANNEX-I-introduction-dpf?tabset-35584=2](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/s/article/ANNEX-I-introduction-dpf?tabset-35584=2) you may invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.

You have the right to access personal data covered by the DPF, and you have the right to correct, amend or request the deletion of such data. You may make requests to access, correct, amend, or request deletion of your data by emailing [deleteme@keepersecurity.com](mailto:deleteme@keepersecurity.com).

Keeper Security remains liable under the DPF if an agent processes Personal data covered by the DPF in a manner inconsistent with the DPF, except where Keeper Security is not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.

Security
--------

Keeper Security hosts its infrastructure with Amazon AWS in a highly secure server environment with 24x7 monitoring, surveillance and support to prevent unauthorized access and data security. Advanced security measures including firewalls, security guards and surveillance are taken to ensure the continued service and protection of your data from natural disaster, intruders and disruptive events. More information about AWS Cloud Security can be found at [https://aws.amazon.com/security/](https://aws.amazon.com/security/).

Data Encryption
---------------

Keeper is a Zero Knowledge security provider. Zero Knowledge is a system architecture that guarantees the highest levels of security and privacy by adhering to the following principles:

1. Data is encrypted and decrypted at the device level (not on the server)
2. The application never stores plain text (human readable) data
3. The server never receives data in plain text
4. No Keeper employee or 3rd party can view the unencrypted data
5. The keys to decrypt and encrypt data are derived from the user’s master password
6. Multi-Layer encryption provides access control at the user, group and admin level
7. Sharing of data uses Public Key Cryptography for secure key distribution
8. Data is encrypted locally on the user’s device before it is transmitted and stored in Keeper’s Cloud Security Vault. When data is synchronized to another device, the data remains encrypted until it is decrypted on the other device.

Keeper software runs on iPhone\*, iPad\*, iPod\*, Android\*, Android Tablets\*, Windows\*, Mac OS\* and Linux\* operating systems. (\*Note: These trade names are protected by the registered trademarks of their respective owners. Keeper and Password Keeper are U.S. registered trademarks of Keeper Security, Inc.).

For more detailed information about Keeper's security model, please visit: [https://keepersecurity.com/security](https://keepersecurity.com/security). For details about Keeper’s encryption model, please visit [https://docs.keeper.io/enterprise-guide/keeper-encryption-model](https://docs.keeper.io/enterprise-guide/keeper-encryption-model).

Information We Collect
----------------------

Keeper Security does not have access to, or the ability to decrypt your vault. Our Zero-Knowledge encryption model ensures that only you can decrypt your stored information.

Keeper Security collects limited personal information from customers who register with our services including a username or email address and phone number for the purpose of account verification and two-factor authentication. If a customer decides to subscribe to our service, we may collect credit card information which is tokenized and used for payment processing, but not stored. We use the customer registration information to authenticate users and provide access to services at [https://keepersecurity.com](https://keepersecurity.com/). As with any cloud-based services, when you download and use our product we automatically collect information on the type of device you use, operating system version, a randomly-generated device identifier, system performance information and IP address. We also use the email addresses used in the registration information to communicate with our users. When you register for a subscription to Keeper software, you automatically "opt-in" to receive email communication from us which shall concur with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003.

End-users of Keeper Enterprise will not receive consumer marketing email communications from us but may receive important communications related to changes to services, maintenance notifications and security-related events. Keeper consumer end-users periodically may receive email communications from us regarding changes to our services, maintenance notifications, promotional materials and important security-related events. You will be permitted at any time to "opt-out" of the receipt of email communications related to marketing and promotional material. The "opt-out" page can be viewed here: [https://keepersecurity.com/unsubscribe](https://keepersecurity.com/unsubscribe). In the event you opt-out from receiving marketing and promotional material, we may, as necessary, email you in connection with a purchase confirmation, customer support matter or security issue related to your account. Keeper Security will never have access to your Master Password or records stored within your Keeper Vault.

If you choose to allow other people to access a Keeper Vault record, we will ask you for that person's email address. We will automatically send this person a one-time email inviting them to visit the site and application. If you also choose to register a deal under a partner program, we will ask for your prospect's name, email, phone number and company information. Keeper Security stores this information to send this one-time email.

If the assigned person or your prospect chooses to decline, s/he may contact us at [deleteme@keepersecurity.com](mailto:deleteme@keepersecurity.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

Keeper Security collects and logs aggregate user statistics and website traffic. Such information includes website traffic statistics, date and time of visits, browser type used to access the service, frequency of visits and to which pages, etc. We use this information to improve the services delivered to our customers, to track and diagnose performance problems and administer the website.

Keeper Security does not have access to or knowledge of an account holder’s master password, encryption keys or access to his or her Keeper vault. Accordingly, any account disclosure required by law, under a subpoena, would be limited to general account information such as the account holder’s name and account term. Keeper Security may disclose aggregated user statistics (for example, 50% of Keeper Security customers use the service daily) in order to describe our services to prospective partners, affiliates and other third parties for lawful purposes. Keeper Security will never disclose such data on an individual or identifiable basis to third parties except when we must comply with laws that require such disclosure to law enforcement authorities or other government third party officials such as subpoenas, or we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others and to investigate fraud.

Keeper Security transmits limited personal information on vendor-sourced software, under strict confidentiality and security protocols, to provide essential business services including customer support, account management, analytics, payment processing and live chat. Information we share is limited to email address and IP address.

Keeper Security has data protection agreements with its vendors which limit the use of customer information to essential business functions. Keeper Security does not sell, market or transact upon user information outside of its cybersecurity operations.

If Keeper Security is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

We may provide limited contact, payment and usage information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as our live chat customer support or analytics provider. These companies are authorized to use such information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

Keeper Security will only collect, use and disclose information to provide the services to the customer, to provide customer support or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. Keeper Security will offer individuals the opportunity to choose (opt-out) whether their personal information is (a) to be disclosed to a non-agent third party, or (b) to be used for a purpose other than the purpose for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by the individual. Keeper Security will provide individuals with reasonable mechanisms to exercise their choices.

Keeper Security permits the upload of images, videos and files as a feature of the application. All images, videos and files uploaded to the application are encrypted and Keeper Security cannot access the uploaded content.

How to Access Your Personal Data
--------------------------------

Upon request Keeper Security will provide any users regardless of location with information about whether we hold, or process on behalf of a third party, any of your personal information. To request this information please contact us at [privacy@keepersecurity.com](mailto:privacy@keepersecurity.com). You may deactivate your Keeper Security account and delete your personally identifiable information at any time by contacting us at [deleteme@keepersecurity.com](mailto:deleteme@keepersecurity.com) clearly indicating that you wish to deactivate and delete such information. If your personal information changes, or you seek to exercise any rights under GDPR or CCPA, please submit the request to Customer Support at [gdpr@keepersecurity.com](mailto:gdpr@keepersecurity.com). In your request, please make clear what personal data is concerned and the change required. We will comply with your request promptly, but in any event within 30 days of your request (45 days for requests under the CCPA). We may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes or to complete transactions that you began prior to requesting such change or deletion.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

In accordance with the European Union General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), Children’s Online Privacy and Protection Act (COPPA) and the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) Keeper Security does not intentionally collect personally identifiable information from nor solicit children under eighteen years of age.

Other than as disclosed in this Privacy Policy, at no time will Keeper Security disclose identifiable personal information to any third parties without your express, written consent. Keeper Security does not sell customer information to third parties for any purpose.

Keeper Security will be permitted to display an active customers' corporate logo on its website for the purpose of promoting both the customer and Keeper Security.

California Consumer Rights Under the CCPA
-----------------------------------------

California Consumers have the following rights under the California Consumer Protection Act (CCPA):

**Right to Notice:** Under the CCPA, businesses must inform consumers at or before the point of collection what categories of personal information will be collected and the purposes for which these categories will be used.

**Right to Access:** Consumers have the right to request that a business disclose the categories of personal information collected; the categories of sources from which personal information is collected; the business or commercial purpose; the categories of third parties with which the business shares personal information; and the specific pieces of personal information the business holds about a consumer.

**Right to Opt-Out:** Consumers have the right—at any time—to direct businesses that sell personal information about the consumer to third parties to stop this sale, known as the right to opt out.

**Right to Request Deletion:** Consumers also have the right to request deletion of personal information, but only where that information was collected from the consumer.

**Right to Equal Services and Prices:** The CCPA prohibits businesses from discriminating against consumers by denying goods or services, charging a different price or rate for goods or services, providing a different level or quality of goods or services, or suggesting that they will do any of these things based upon a consumer’s exercise of any CCPA rights.

For CCPA related inquiries visit this page: [https://keepersecurity.com/contact.html?t=p&r=CCPA](https://keepersecurity.com/contact.html?t=p&r=CCPA)

KeeperFill®
-----------

Keeper Security utilizes a system called KeeperFill® which allows you to autofill login credentials across mobile apps and browsers. When Keeper is preloaded on OEM devices, KeeperFill is automatically enabled to utilize the device's accessibility and input method services to identify mobile apps and websites which require login credentials. As disclosed in the Security Disclosure at [https://keepersecurity.com/security.html](https://keepersecurity.com/security.html), Keeper is a zero-knowledge security platform. As such, Keeper Security cannot access, track or view the activity of KeeperFill or your Keeper records. KeeperFill can be disabled at any time by visiting the accessibility settings screen of your device.

Browser Extension
-----------------

Installation of the Keeper Browser Extension requires explicit permission to read and write login and password data into a user-designated website form fields for the purpose of securely auto-filling credentials from the user’s Keeper Vault. Keeper does not track or store a user’s browsing history or web page usage.

Cookies & Tracking Technologies
-------------------------------

Keeper Security and our marketing partners, affiliates, or analytics or service providers, use technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags, and scripts, to analyze trends, administer the website, tracking users' movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual and aggregated basis.

If the website visitor consents to the use of cookies, Keeper Security uses cookies to store and track information about your usage of our website. Cookies are encrypted and unidentifiable bits of information sent to your browser from a web server that is stored on your computer's hard drive.

We may use cookies to gather aggregated information about user habits on our website. For example, we may use cookies to estimate the number of concurrent users, estimate the total number of users, measure traffic statistics and to better understand how our users are using our site. Cookies are never used to store web-vault authentication information or vault user record data.

You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our website or service.

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data.

We use Local Storage, such as HTML5, to store content information and preferences. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our website or to display advertising based upon your web browsing activity also use HTML5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5.

We partner with a third-party to manage our advertising of Keeper products on other websites. Our third-party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on other websites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. As a result, you may receive advertisements for Keeper products on other third-party websites based on your browsing activity on our website. If you wish to opt out of interest-based advertising visit [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout), [https://optout.aboutads.info/](https://optout.aboutads.info/), and [https://optout.networkadvertising.org/](https://optout.networkadvertising.org/) \[or if located in the European Union visit [https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/](https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)\]. For security and privacy reasons, Keeper Security does not run third-party ads in its application.

Master Password
---------------

It is the user's responsibility to protect the security of their Keeper Master Password. Access to Keeper Security services are protected by a unique username/email and Master Password that is known by you only. Keeper Security has designed internal security processes that encrypt customer passwords to protect it from being divulged or accessed by anyone other than you. Neither Keeper Security employees nor any of its contractors can obtain or access your password. Neither Keeper Security employees nor any of its contractors will ask you for your password via mail, email or telephone nor any other unsolicited manner.

Blogs
-----

Our blog is managed by a third party application that may require you to register to post a comment. We do not have access or control of the information posted to the blog. You will need to contact or login into the third party application if you want the personal information that was posted to the comments section removed. To learn how the third party application uses your information, please review their privacy policy.

Third Party Links
-----------------

When customers and users access and use Keeper Security, there may be links to websites and services operated by third parties. Keeper Security makes no representations or warranties about the policies of third party websites that are linked to Keeper Security or any of its services. Keeper Security recommends that you read the privacy policies posted by those third party websites.

Testimonials
------------

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our website in addition to other endorsements. With your consent, we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [deleteme@keepersecurity.com](mailto:deleteme@keepersecurity.com).

Further Questions
-----------------

If you have further questions about our Privacy Policy, email us at [security@keepersecurity.com](mailto:security@keepersecurity.com).

Keeper Security, Inc.  
333 N Green St.  
Suite 811  
Chicago IL 60607

General
-------

Keeper Security, Inc. ("Keeper Security") is fanatical about protecting your privacy. Keeper Security has created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our commitment to protecting your privacy and to disclose our information and privacy practices for [https://keepersecurity.com](https://keepersecurity.com/) and its services. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

We reserve the right to change this Policy and will notify you of such changes via email or our website. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at [security@keepersecurity.com](mailto:security@keepersecurity.com).

As used in this Privacy Policy, “personal data” or "personal information" has the meaning provided in the EU General Data Protection Regulation of 2018 (the “GDPR”), and includes any information which, either alone or when combined with other information we hold, identifies an individual, such as name, mailing address, email address, IP address and telephone number. For legal residents of the State of California, who are covered by the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”), this definition includes any additional elements defined as such by the CCPA. In addition to meeting GDPR and CCPA compliance requirements, the terms of this privacy policy are applicable to all users regardless of location.

Security
--------

Keeper Security hosts its infrastructure with Amazon AWS in a highly secure server environment with 24x7 monitoring, surveillance and support to prevent unauthorized access and data security. Advanced security measures including firewalls, security guards and surveillance are taken to ensure the continued service and protection of your data from natural disaster, intruders and disruptive events. More information about AWS Cloud Security can be found at [https://aws.amazon.com/security/](https://aws.amazon.com/security/).

Data Encryption
---------------

Keeper is a Zero Knowledge security provider. Zero Knowledge is a system architecture that guarantees the highest levels of security and privacy by adhering to the following principles:

1. Data is encrypted and decrypted at the device level (not on the server)
2. The application never stores plain text (human readable) data
3. The server never receives data in plain text
4. No Keeper employee or 3rd party can view the unencrypted data
5. The keys to decrypt and encrypt data are derived from the user’s master password
6. Multi-Layer encryption provides access control at the user, group and admin level
7. Sharing of data uses Public Key Cryptography for secure key distribution
8. Data is encrypted locally on the user’s device before it is transmitted and stored in Keeper’s Cloud Security Vault. When data is synchronized to another device, the data remains encrypted until it is decrypted on the other device.

Keeper software runs on iPhone\*, iPad\*, iPod\*, Android\*, Android Tablets\*, Windows\*, Mac OS\* and Linux\* operating systems. (\*Note: These trade names are protected by the registered trademarks of their respective owners. Keeper and Password Keeper are U.S. registered trademarks of Keeper Security, Inc.).

For more detailed information about Keeper's security model, please visit: [https://keepersecurity.com/security](https://keepersecurity.com/security).

Information We Collect
----------------------

Keeper Security does not have access to, or the ability to decrypt your vault. Our Zero-Knowledge encryption model ensures that only you can decrypt your stored information.

Keeper Security collects limited personal information from customers who register with our services including a username or email address and phone number for the purpose of account verification and two-factor authentication. If a customer decides to subscribe to our service, we may collect credit card information which is tokenized and used for payment processing, but not stored. We use the customer registration information to authenticate users and provide access to services at [https://keepersecurity.com](https://keepersecurity.com/). As with any cloud-based services, when you download and use our product we automatically collect information on the type of device you use, operating system version, a randomly-generated device identifier, system performance information and IP address. We also use the email addresses used in the registration information to communicate with our users. When you register for a subscription to Keeper software, you automatically "opt-in" to receive email communication from us which shall concur with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003.

End-users of Keeper Enterprise will not receive consumer marketing email communications from us but may receive important communications related to changes to services, maintenance notifications and security-related events. Keeper consumer end-users periodically may receive email communications from us regarding changes to our services, maintenance notifications, promotional materials and important security-related events. You will be permitted at any time to "opt-out" of the receipt of email communications related to marketing and promotional material. The "opt-out" page can be viewed here: [https://keepersecurity.com/unsubscribe](https://keepersecurity.com/unsubscribe). In the event you opt-out from receiving marketing and promotional material, we may, as necessary, email you in connection with a purchase confirmation, customer support matter or security issue related to your account. Keeper Security will never have access to your Master Password or records stored within your Keeper Vault.

If you choose to allow other people to access a Keeper Vault record, we will ask you for that person's email address. We will automatically send this person a one-time email inviting them to visit the site and application. If you also choose to register a deal under a partner program, we will ask for your prospect's name, email, phone number and company information. Keeper Security stores this information to send this one-time email.

If the assigned person or your prospect chooses to decline, s/he may contact us at [deleteme@keepersecurity.com](mailto:deleteme@keepersecurity.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

Keeper Security collects and logs aggregate user statistics and website traffic. Such information includes website traffic statistics, date and time of visits, browser type used to access the service, frequency of visits and to which pages, etc. We use this information to improve the services delivered to our customers, to track and diagnose performance problems and administer the website.

Keeper Security does not have access to or knowledge of an account holder’s master password, encryption keys or access to his or her Keeper vault. Accordingly, any account disclosure required by law, under a subpoena, would be limited to general account information such as the account holder’s name and account term. Keeper Security may disclose aggregated user statistics (for example, 50% of Keeper Security customers use the service daily) in order to describe our services to prospective partners, affiliates and other third parties for lawful purposes. Keeper Security will never disclose such data on an individual or identifiable basis to third parties except when we must comply with laws that require such disclosure to law enforcement authorities or other government third party officials such as subpoenas, or we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others and to investigate fraud.

Keeper Security transmits limited personal information on vendor-sourced software, under strict confidentiality and security protocols, to provide essential business services including customer support, account management, analytics, payment processing and live chat. Information we share is limited to email address and IP address.

Keeper Security has data protection agreements with its vendors which limit the use of customer information to essential business functions. Keeper Security does not sell, market or transact upon user information outside of its cybersecurity operations.

If Keeper Security is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

We may provide limited contact, payment and usage information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as our live chat customer support or analytics provider. These companies are authorized to use such information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

Keeper Security permits the upload of images, videos and files as a feature of the application. All images, videos and files uploaded to the application are encrypted and Keeper Security cannot access the uploaded content.

How to Access Your Personal Data
--------------------------------

Upon request Keeper Security will provide any users regardless of location with information about whether we hold, or process on behalf of a third party, any of your personal information. To request this information please contact us at [privacy@keepersecurity.com](mailto:privacy@keepersecurity.com). You may deactivate your Keeper Security account and delete your personally identifiable information at any time by contacting us at [deleteme@keepersecurity.com](mailto:deleteme@keepersecurity.com) clearly indicating that you wish to deactivate and delete such information. If your personal information changes, or you seek to exercise any rights under GDPR or CCPA, please submit the request to Customer Support at [gdpr@keepersecurity.com](mailto:gdpr@keepersecurity.com). In your request, please make clear what personal data is concerned and the change required. We will comply with your request promptly, but in any event within 30 days of your request (45 days for requests under the CCPA). We may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes or to complete transactions that you began prior to requesting such change or deletion.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

In accordance with the European Union General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), Children’s Online Privacy and Protection Act (COPPA) and the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) Keeper Security does not intentionally collect personally identifiable information from nor solicit children under eighteen years of age.

Other than as disclosed in this Privacy Policy, at no time will Keeper Security disclose identifiable personal information to any third parties without your express, written consent. Keeper Security does not sell customer information to third parties for any purpose.

Keeper Security will be permitted to display an active customers' corporate logo on its website for the purpose of promoting both the customer and Keeper Security.

California Consumer Rights Under the CCPA
-----------------------------------------

California Consumers have the following rights under the California Consumer Protection Act (CCPA):

**Right to Notice:** Under the CCPA, businesses must inform consumers at or before the point of collection what categories of personal information will be collected and the purposes for which these categories will be used.

**Right to Access:** Consumers have the right to request that a business disclose the categories of personal information collected; the categories of sources from which personal information is collected; the business or commercial purpose; the categories of third parties with which the business shares personal information; and the specific pieces of personal information the business holds about a consumer.

**Right to Opt-Out:** Consumers have the right—at any time—to direct businesses that sell personal information about the consumer to third parties to stop this sale, known as the right to opt out.

**Right to Request Deletion:** Consumers also have the right to request deletion of personal information, but only where that information was collected from the consumer.

**Right to Equal Services and Prices:** The CCPA prohibits businesses from discriminating against consumers by denying goods or services, charging a different price or rate for goods or services, providing a different level or quality of goods or services, or suggesting that they will do any of these things based upon a consumer’s exercise of any CCPA rights.

For CCPA related inquiries visit this page: [https://keepersecurity.com/contact.html?t=p&r=CCPA](https://keepersecurity.com/contact.html?t=p&r=CCPA)

KeeperFill®
-----------

Keeper Security utilizes a system called KeeperFill® which allows you to autofill login credentials across mobile apps and browsers. When Keeper is preloaded on OEM devices, KeeperFill is automatically enabled to utilize the device's accessibility and input method services to identify mobile apps and websites which require login credentials. As disclosed in the Security Disclosure at [https://keepersecurity.com/security.html](https://keepersecurity.com/security.html), Keeper is a zero-knowledge security platform. As such, Keeper Security cannot access, track or view the activity of KeeperFill or your Keeper records. KeeperFill can be disabled at any time by visiting the accessibility settings screen of your device.

Browser Extension
-----------------

Installation of the Keeper Browser Extension requires explicit permission to read and write login and password data into a user-designated website form fields for the purpose of securely auto-filling credentials from the user’s Keeper Vault. Keeper does not track or store a user’s browsing history or web page usage.

Cookies & Tracking Technologies
-------------------------------

Keeper Security and our marketing partners, affiliates, or analytics or service providers, use technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags, and scripts, to analyze trends, administer the website, tracking users' movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual and aggregated basis.

If the website visitor consents to the use of cookies, Keeper Security uses cookies to store and track information about your usage of our website. Cookies are encrypted and unidentifiable bits of information sent to your browser from a web server that is stored on your computer's hard drive.

We may use cookies to gather aggregated information about user habits on our website. For example, we may use cookies to estimate the number of concurrent users, estimate the total number of users, measure traffic statistics and to better understand how our users are using our site. Cookies are never used to store web-vault authentication information or vault user record data.

You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our website or service.

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data.

We use Local Storage, such as HTML5, to store content information and preferences. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our website or to display advertising based upon your web browsing activity also use HTML5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5.

We partner with a third-party to manage our advertising of Keeper products on other websites. Our third-party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on other websites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. As a result, you may receive advertisements for Keeper products on other third-party websites based on your browsing activity on our website. If you wish to opt out of interest-based advertising visit [https://keepersecurity.com/contact.html?t=p&r=general](https://keepersecurity.com/contact.html?t=p&r=general) \[if located in the European Union visit [https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/](https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)\]. For security and privacy purposes, Keeper Security does not run third-party ads in its application.

Master Password
---------------

It is the user's responsibility to protect the security of their Keeper Master Password. Access to Keeper Security services are protected by a unique username/email and Master Password that is known by you only. Keeper Security has designed internal security processes that encrypt customer passwords to protect it from being divulged or accessed by anyone other than you. Neither Keeper Security employees nor any of its contractors can obtain or access your password. Neither Keeper Security employees nor any of its contractors will ask you for your password via mail, email or telephone nor any other unsolicited manner.

Blogs
-----

Our blog is managed by a third party application that may require you to register to post a comment. We do not have access or control of the information posted to the blog. You will need to contact or login into the third party application if you want the personal information that was posted to the comments section removed. To learn how the third party application uses your information, please review their privacy policy.

Third Party Links
-----------------

When customers and users access and use Keeper Security, there may be links to websites and services operated by third parties. Keeper Security makes no representations or warranties about the policies of third party websites that are linked to Keeper Security or any of its services. Keeper Security recommends that you read the privacy policies posted by those third party websites.

Testimonials
------------

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our website in addition to other endorsements. With your consent, we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [deleteme@keepersecurity.com](mailto:deleteme@keepersecurity.com).

Further Questions
-----------------

If you have further questions about our Privacy Policy, email us at [security@keepersecurity.com](mailto:security@keepersecurity.com).

Keeper Security, Inc.  
333 N Green St.  
Suite 811  
Chicago, IL 60607
